most pick which is also made from
莫氏硬度针，它也是由
plastic we start seeing some indentions
塑料制成 我们开始看到一些压痕
and deformations at a level two with
和变形，在二级时，伴随着
deeper grooves at a level three the
在三级时更深的凹槽
entire screen of the MXT ultimate both
MXT ultimate的整个屏幕，包括
inner and outer is fingernail
内部和外部，都是指甲
scratchable levels of plastic which of
可刮花的塑料级别，这当然
course is not a deel breaker just good
当然不是一个致命缺陷，只是好的
information to have plastic is not
信息需要了解 塑料并非
necessarily a bad thing but just like
必然是坏事，但这就像
you wouldn't hang drywall wearing a
你不会戴着一块
Rolex or take a Lambo off-roading
劳力士去挂石膏板，或者开着兰博基尼去越野
actually that does sound kind of fun but
实际上那听起来确实有点有趣，但是
all I'm saying is as a daily driver the
我想说的是，作为日常主力机，这款
M XT requires clean pockets and a bit of
M XT需要干净的口袋和一点点
extra attention the inner 8 megapixel
额外的注意 内置的800万像素
selfie camera which I won't touch with
自拍摄像头，我不会用我的
my Razor is covered with that same soft
剃刀去碰它，它被同样柔软的
plastic with the screen turned off the
塑料覆盖着，当屏幕关闭时
scratch marks from my fingernails and
我的指甲和
plastic tools appear even more visual
塑料工具留下的划痕看起来更加明显
ually apparent I don't want the soft
我不希望这块软屏
screen to distract from what a
分散了人们对它是一项多么
phenomenal technological achievement
非凡技术成就的注意力
this phone has accomplished cuz for
这款手机已经完成，因为作为
reference if you remember Apple also
参考，如果你还记得苹果公司也
made their thinnest product ever this
在今年推出了他们有史以来最薄的产品
year with the iPad Pro at 5.1 mm thick
即iPad Pro，厚度为5.1毫米
this MXT ultimate clocks in at four it's
这款MXT ultimate的厚度达到了4毫米，它
quite mindblowing to
真是令人难以置信
hold the frame appears to be made from
拿住看，框架似乎是由
aluminum including the hinge
铝制成，包括铰链
nibblets the M XT does have stereo
的小部件。M XT确实有立体声
loudspeakers the right side of the phone
扬声器。手机的右侧
has the metal volume rocker as well as a
有金属音量键以及一个
side mounted fingerprint scanner inside
侧面安装的指纹扫描仪，位于
that power
那个电源
button the three sides of the bottom
按钮内。底部的三个侧面
contain another loudspeaker a 66 W USBC
包含另一个扬声器，一个66瓦的USBC
Port that's capable of 5w reverse wire
端口，能够进行5瓦反向有线
charging and a few microphones we do
充电和几个麦克风。我们确实
have a SIM card tray which does have a
有一个SIM卡托盘，它确实有一个
gray rubber ring around the opening but
开口周围有灰色橡胶圈，但是
no official IP or dust resistant rating
没有官方的IP或防尘等级
it's wild to see however that the
然而，看到那个
thickness of the physical USB cable that
我插入手机的实体USB数据线的厚度
I'm plugging into the phone is actually
实际上比手机本身还要厚
thicker than the phone itself it's like
这就像是科幻电影里的
technology out of a science fiction
技术一样。而且还有传言说
movie also there are rumors of a global
这款M XT ultimate将于2025年
launch for this m XT ultimate in 2025
全球发布，当然前提是
assuming of course that we're all still
我们都还在这里。
here making our way over to the back the
转到背面，这款手机唯一厚的部分
only part of this phone that's thick is
是摄像头凸起。我们有一个1200万像素的
the camera bump we have a 12 megapixel
超广角摄像头在左上角
Ultra wide camera in the top left corner
主摄是5000万像素可变光圈镜头
the main 50 megap variable aperture lens
在底部，而1200万像素的5倍
is on the bottom and the 12 megap 5
长焦镜头在右上角
times telephoto is in the upper right
下方是激光自动对焦模块。所有这些
with the laser autofocus below that all
都位于星钻设计的大马士革钢外观的
all of which are sitting inside the star
摄像头凸起中。红色的皮革，我
Diamond designed Damascus steel looking
不确定是不是真皮，但肯定
camera bump the red leather which I'm
有很好的纹理手感，而且镶嵌的
not sure if it's real or not definitely
华为品牌标志和ultimate design
has a nice textured feel and the inlaid
字样不会自行脱落或掉出。
Huawei branding and ultimate design
在这块面板下方有一个50瓦的无线
script won't be falling out or coming
充电板，我们或许有幸
out on its own there's a 50 W wireless
稍后能看到它。中间的面板是空白的
charging pad underneath this panel which
而远端的面板上有一个由华为设计和制造的
we might be lucky enough to see here in
徽章嵌入皮革中。
a second the center panel is blank and
这个徽章是金属制成的。内部折叠的
the far panel has a designed and crafted
铰链，类似于三星折叠手机的
by Huawei token embedded into the
转轴部分，是金属制成的，而外部折叠的
leather the token is made from metal the
铰链的转轴部分是软屏材质
internally folding hinge similar to the
这意味着我现在还不会去刮它。
spine on Samsung's folding phone is made
然而，摄像头单元周围的大马士革外观钢圈
from metal while the externally folding
是金属制成的。完全展开的M XT
hinge has the soft screen on the spine
ultimate拥有3K分辨率、90Hz LTPO
which means I'm not going to scratch it
OLED屏幕，支持10亿色彩。背景中的蓝鸟
just yet the Damascus looking steel ring
看起来有点像那个被谋杀之前的
around the camera units however is made
推特鸟。在火焰下，屏幕大约能坚持10秒
from metal the fully unfolded M XT
才开始变色，表层
ultimate has a 3K resolution 90 HZ ltpo
简直是融化了。华为承诺
OLED with 1 billion colors the blue J in
外屏的顶层符合免费
the background looks kind of like that
更换的条件，但屏幕本身，比如
Twitter bird before it was murdered
像素部分，如果在保修期外损坏
under Flame the screen last for about 10
维修费用大约需要1100美元
seconds before discoloring and the
这比我预想的要少得出奇。
surface layer literally melting huaw has
现在记住，我并非以破坏或
promised that the top layer of the
毁坏设备为乐。我只是在此
external screen is eligible for free
雄辩地科普电子产品的耐用性
Replacements but the screen itself like
通常情况下，如果一部普通智能手机意外地
the pixel part of it if damaged outside
被沙子覆盖，那并不会是世界末日
of warranty would cost about $1,100 to
玻璃上可能会因为石英或其他硬质矿物
fix which is surprisingly less than I
产生一些微小的划痕或磨损
thought it would be now remember I do
但在骨料中，但最终它会
not Delight in the destruction or
没事的。不过对于折叠屏手机来说
decimation of devices I'm just here to
尤其是一款像这样高端且精密调校的
eloquently educate on the endurance of
沙子就是死刑判决
electronics where Norm normally if a
并非来自折叠屏本身